or for some reason, before the Poles, the Germans all all
или почему-то до поляки немцы все все
countries hate these unloadings,
страны ненавидят разгрузки
but the Germans are good, so the Germans, on the contrary, and the
но немцы хорошо так немцы наоборот а
French
французы
universities of the British imposed sanctions there, the
вузы британцев санкции наложили там
Americans, what are they
американцы они что же
[music]
[музыка]
then
тогда
it’s possible when Napoleon attacked the Soviet Union
можно когда наполеон на советский союз
on
на
children’s laughter yes
детский смех да
here it is
вот он
[music  ] I
[музыка]
don’t have a husband, so we’re talking about different ones, so I’m
нет мужа так про разные говорим вот мне
just wondering when Napoleon
просто интересно вот когда наполеон
attacked the Soviet Union, he lost,
напал на советский союз он проиграл
but
проиграл да а
let’s say why he lost,
скажем из-за чего он проиграл
yes, exactly, yes, by the way, there was a battle on the ice
да точно да кстати да ледовое побоище
there, Prince Alexander Nevsky, he
там князь александр невский он
beat Napoleon of the Soviet Union, yes, on
советского союза побил наполеона да на
Lake
озере
Ladoga  in my opinion, or some kind of lake
ладожское по моему или какое-то озеро
, I don’t remember Lake Ladoga before the prize of the
было не помню ладожского озера до приз
waves,
волн а
why does everyone dislike Russians so much, here are the fields,
почему все так не любят русски вот поля
Ukrainians, bad Poles, fleas, Germans,
украинцы плохие поляки блохи немцы
why everyone doesn’t like Russians so much, because of
почему все так русских не любят из-за
what they become the
чего становятся
most interesting thing is that as far as we
самое интересное то что на сколько мы
know,
знаем
you know  you are the story of
знаете ли вы историю
when europe
когда европа
germany
германия
from 39 world countries from 39 to 45 it was
из 39 стран мировая с 39 по 45 было
like this to look at troy the world war
так смотреть в трой мировая война
began the german attack on poland at
началась нападение германии на польшу в
three  twenty-ninth year germany
тридцать девятом году германия
and when it’s
а когда
good and how did the second world
хорошо а с чего началась вторая мировая
war start then with a rapier
война тогда с рапиру
[music]
[музыка]
stockton and let’s on the map between
стоктон а давайте на карте между
germany and the soviet union what else
германией и советским союзом что еще
is
есть
further here is poland between germany and the
дальше вот польши между германией и
soviet union and there is poland
советским союзом и есть польше а
but how how did germany attack  to the Soviet
а как как германия напала на советский
Union through you remember
союз через помнишь
shish it’s
шиш он
not well Poland and Germany to me there the Germans
не ну польше и германии to me там немцы
there are dancing different countries
там плятит разные страны
and where do you twitch and then you hear the
а где вы дергаетесь и тогда слышно
old map disappears on the old map show Poland
старая карта по старой карте шоу польше
and Germany it was the same thing
и германии это одно и то же было
who said that
кто сказал что
Wikipedia see the second  the world
википедии посмотрите вторая мировая
war of the doctor from September 1, 3 from the ninth
война врача с 1 сентября 3 с девятого
year of
года
41 years,
41 года
and
а
that is, it turns out that Germany did not attack Poland
то есть получается германия на польше не
in the thirty-ninth year,
нападала в тридцать девятом году так
so look
вот смотри
Poland the Soviet Union in 39 Germany
польша советский союз в 39 германия
attacked Poland and the Second
напала на польшу и началась вторая
World War began, the
мировая война
Soviet Union also attacked Poland
советский союз тоже напал на польшу
took part  Poland and the
забрал часть польши и
border of the Soviet Union and Germany
граница советского союза и германии
turned out to be the Third Reich, the whole
получилось третьего рейха весь вот пакт
Molotov-Ribbentrop Pact was taught from history,
молотова-риббентропа учили по истории
remember this
помните такое
here it’s not about Poland, even if it doesn’t hurt anymore,
тут дело не в польше даже даже больше не
then the war is
задевают то война
good, but these Bandera burned out
хорошо а вот эти погорели бандеры что
what Bandera does in Ukraine what is yours like
там бандеры делает в украине какова ваша
to attack Ukraine,
надо нападать на украину
well, what does it do
ну что она делает
they
они
burned
сжигали
and now it looks like they were doing
а сейчас выглядит делались
and killing they don’t burn it can be done
и убивает не сжигают может быть делать
to this day  day,
по сей день
well, the one for which they attacked
ну тот для чего напали
nowhere protects they came in Russian
никуда защищает пришли in русский
well, these Bandera killed their people and
хорошо их людей эти бандеры убили и
burned
сожгли
it, according to it, it’s
это согласно
very relevant when just this
актуально очень когда просто вот этот
srach between Ukrainians and
срач между украинцами и
Russians was when you submitted a video they
россиянами было когда вы подали видео их
were called in general used to be called
называли вообще раньше называли
satanists, I personally saw these videos in
сатанистами я видела лично эти видео в
2014  the year when
2014 году когда
with the Russian flag and the child, that is,
с российским флагом и ребенок то есть
once again that there was
еще раз что там было
not a handle, the leg did not understand about the child, the theme of the
не ручка ножка не понял про ребенка тему
Russian
российский флаг
minecraft flag is true and the child lies on it, the
minecraft верно и на нем лежит ребенок
Russian child,
российский ребенок
how to destroy,
как уничтожить
did not even see
даже не видел
find joy, it
найти радости
’s a matter
тут дело
of ecumenical, a very good fellow
во вселенский очень хороший молодец
decided in the end
решил в итоге
that is, you would Judy it turns out so these
то есть вы бы джуди получается так эти
military operations in Ukraine
военные действия в украине
wait about what Zelinsk threatened  and
подождите о чем в чем угрожал зелинский
you will be specifically what you support
вам будут конкретно что вы поддерживаете
this
это
bandera
бандеры
you are aware of ukraine is aware of all these are such
вы в курсе украина в курсе все это такие
coopers this group can
бондаря эта группировка
remember 2014, it
вспомнить 2014 год тоже
can also go when you
может идет когда
suddenly
вдруг
join NATO, that is, what does it mean
вступить в нато то есть что это значит
should
надо
Ukraine, that is, specifically,
украины то есть конкретно
Ukraine close to those
украина приближенной к те
well, look here
хорошо смотрите вот
latvia and lithuania estonia a niche for that
латвия и литва эстония нишу на то
over them they are right near moscow near
ним над они прям возле москвы возле
petersburg than ukraine would be worse
питера чем украина была бы страшнее
ukraine far from moscow from petersburg
украина далеко от москвы от питера
well yes well the baltic countries they are even closer
ну да ну страны балтии они еще ближе
why they filed something given to the side or
ну почему подали то данное стороне или
tula for recently nothing inside but then
тула для недавно уже внутри ничего но то
there  russia didn't make
там россии не делал
any changes if someone noticed how
изменения если кто-то заметил как
clicking we have about 6000 stations on
водя щелчок у нас около 6000 станций на
and 20 countries we are fighting against
а 20 стран мы боремся против
20 countries one country
20 стран одна страна
sanctions precisely because of the hostilities
санкций именно из-за военных действиях
in
на на украине
ukraine including europe i.e. it is normal for them
в том числе европа то есть для них это
5 russians
5 русских